probably say that the computations of a
可以说一个神经网络的计算
【翻译：刘振卫 审核/时间轴：AcceptedDoge】
neural network are all organized in
都是按照
terms of a forward path or a forward
前向或反向传播过程组织的
propagation step, in which we compute the
其中首先我们计算出
output of the new network followed by a
一个新的网络的输出（前向过程）
backward pass or a back complication
紧接着进行一个反向传输操作
step which we use to compute gradients
后者我们用来计算出对应的梯度
or compute derivatives. the computation
或者导数 这个计算图
graph explains why it is organized this
解释了为什么我们用这样的方式这样组织
way, in this video we'll go through an
在这个视频中 我们将看一个例子
example in order to illustrate the
为了阐明这个计算过程
computation graph. let's use a simpler
让我们举一个比逻辑回归
example than logistic regression or a
更加简单的 或者说
informal neural network. let's say that
不那么正式的神经网络的例子
we're trying to compute a function J
我们尝试计算函数J
which is a function of three variables a
J是由三个变量a,b,c组成的函数
B and C and let's say that function is
这个函数是
three times a plus B times C, computing
3(a+b*c)
this function actually has three
计算这个函数实际上有三个
distinct steps, the first is you need to
不同的步骤，第一个首先是
compute what is B times C and let's say
计算b乘以c
we store that in a variable called u so
我们把它储存在变量u中
U is equal to B times C and then you
因此u=b*c
might compute v is equal a times u (a+u), so
然后计算v=a+u(原字幕口误)
let's say you know this is V and then
这就是v
finally your output J is 3 times V so
最后输出J就是3*v
this is your final function J you trying
这就是要计算的函数J
to compute we can take these three steps
我们可以把这三步
and draw them in a computation graph as follows
画成如下的计算图
let's say I draw your three variables a
我先在这画三个变量a,b,c
B and C here so the first thing we did
第一步就是
was compute u equals B times C I'm going
计算u=b*c
to put a rectangular box around that and
我在这周围放个矩形框
so the inputs of that are B and C and
它的输入是b,c
then you might have V equals a plus u so
接着第二步，v=a+u
the inputs to that ah  so the inputs to
因此这个的输入就是，，额，，
that are u which we just computed
刚才计算出来的u
together with a and then finally we have
还有a，最后一步
J equals three times v so as I can
J=3*v
for example a equals five B equals 3
举个例子：a=5,b=3,
and C equals two, then u equals BC would
c=2，u=bc
be six, V equals a plus u be five plus
就是6,v=a+u，就是5+
six and eleven J is three times v so J
6，就是11。J是三倍的v，因此
is equal to 33 and and indeed hope you
J就等于33
can verify that you know this is a three
你应该明白这是
times five plus three times two and if
3*（5+3*2）
you expand that out
如果你把它算出来
you know you actually get thirty three
实际上得到33
has the value of J so the computation
就是J的值，因此这个
graph comes in handy when there is some
计算图用起来很方便 当有
distinguished or some special output
不同的或者一些特殊的输出变量时
variable such as J in this case that you
（如你想要优化的J）
want to optimize and in the case of the
并且在逻辑回归中
logistic regression J is of course the
J也是我们想要
cost function that we're trying to
最小化的代价函数
minimize and what we've seen in this
我们从这个小例子中
little example is that through a
可以看出 通过一个
left-to-right pause you can compute the
从左向右的过程 你可以计算出
value of J and what we'll see in the
J的值 并且在接下来的幻灯片中
next couple slides is that in order to
我们会看到
compute derivatives
为了计算导数
Opa right to left pause like this kind
从右到左的这个过程
of going in the opposite direction as
（和这个蓝色箭头的过程相反）
the blue arrows that would be most
这会是
natural for computing the derivatives so
用于计算导数最自然的方式，因此
the recap the computation graph
概括一下：计算图
organizes a computation with this blue
组织计算的形式 是用蓝色箭头
arrow left to right computation, lets
从左到右的计算 让我们
defer to the next video how you can do
看看下一个视频怎么做
the backward red arrow right to left
这个反向红色箭头 也就是从右到左
computation of the derivatives, let's go
的导数计算 让我们继续
on to the next video
下一个视频